{
    "subject": "resource/Hod_Stuart",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/Bay_of_Quinte",
    "human_readable": "Hod Stuart died in Bay of Quinte.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7984000444412231,
            "question": "Where did Hod Stuart die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.699801504611969,
            "question": "When did Hod Stuart die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35091453790664673,
            "question": "Is there a notable memorial for Hod Stuart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33363816142082214,
            "question": "Were there any famous people born in the Bay of Quinte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27333810925483704,
            "question": "What is the Bay of Quinte known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26055893301963806,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Hod Stuart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2538978159427643,
            "question": "Are there any historical events associated with the Bay of Quinte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23759040236473083,
            "question": "What was Hod Stuart's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17669197916984558,
            "question": "What are some popular activities in the Bay of Quinte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1479613035917282,
            "question": "What is the geography like around the Bay of Quinte?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hod Stuart died in Bay of Quinte.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6582_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular activities in the Bay of Quinte?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6582_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Hod Stuart's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6582_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any historical events associated with the Bay of Quinte?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6582_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6582_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6582_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6582_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6582_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6582_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6582_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6582_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6582_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6582_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6582_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents contain information that confirms Hod Stuart's death occurred in the Bay of Quinte. Specifically, document 21 mentions that \"Hod Stuart died in a diving accident in June 1907\", and document 16 states that \"He suffered a fractured skull and a broken neck, and was said to have died instantly\" in a diving accident in the Bay of Quinte on June 23, 1907."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}